(GPS:)Three-digit route numbers
indicate bypasses or spurs.
(Howard:)Look, Leonard, there's a bridge.
Drive off it.
(Raj:)You know, we're not that far
from Vasquez Rocks.
(Sheldon:)Oh, they shot a lot of
Star Trek episodes out there.
We got our costumes in the trunk...
(Howard:)...we could go there
and have a little photo shoot.
(Raj:)Great idea. I haven't had
a carbohydrate in two weeks.
(Raj:)These cheekbones need to be in front of a
camera before I eat a pretzel and they're gone.
- It sounds fun.
- Oh, smashing.
(Sheldon:)Now, Leonard,
do you know how to get there?
(Sheldon:)- No.
- Yeah, well, luckily, someone in the car does.
(GPS:)Recalculating.
(GPS:)While we're waiting,
do you know which president...
(GPS:)...signed the
Interstate Highway System Act into law?
(GPS:)The answer coming up in 14 miles.
(Sheldon:)None of you will get it. It's Eisenhower.